<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dyslexia</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="dyslexia_desc">Dyslexia is a specific learning disability that is neurobiological in origin. It is characterized by difficulties with accurate and/or fluent word recognition and by poor spelling and decoding abilities."</string>
    <string name="dys_about"><p>Dyslexia refers to a neurobiological learning disability negatively affecting fluent word recognition, spelling and decoding during reading. Dyslexia is a result of the way the brain is wired, making it difficult to process sounds heard in spoken language.</p><p> This app that allows the user to identify difficulties that may lead to diagnosis of Dyslexia.
        User will give assessments of selected Dyslexia category. Our application provides assessments for four types of Dyslexia: Phonological Dyslexia, Visual Dyslexia, Dyscalculia Dyslexia, Dysgraphia Dyslexia</p> </string>
    <string name="dyscalculia">Dyscalculia is a learning disability in math. People with dyscalculia have trouble with math at many levels. They often struggle with key concepts like bigger vs. smaller. And they can have a hard time doing basic math problems and more abstract math.</string>
    <string name="emptyString" />
    <string name="section1_desc">Section 1 of Dyscalculia test includes questions in which user will count the number of objets shown on the screen</string>
    <string name="GeneralTestDescription">The purpose of this test is to detect which type of Dyslexia a user may have.This test have four levels</string>
    <string name="GeneralPhonoTest">Section 1 of General Test includes questions in which user will recognise the sound of single letters/words or Rhyming words</string>
    <string name="generalVisual">Now, this section show the question to detect Visual Dyslexia. This test allows user to select a correct colour option based on text\'s colour or select the correct text as shown on the screen</string>

    <string-array name="myclass">
        <item>1st Class</item>
        <item>2nd Class</item>
        <item>3rd Class</item>
        <item>4th Class</item>
        <item>5th Class</item>
        <item>6th Class</item>
        <item>7th Class</item>
        <item>8th Class</item>
        <item>9th Class</item>
        <item>10th Class</item>
        <item>11th Class</item>
        <item>12 Class</item>
        <item>Adult</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>
